

+977-9823148005



lamak540@gmail.com



Roshi Rural Municipality, Nepal



https://www.facebook.com/kiran.lam a.9615



https://www.linkedin.com/in/kiran-lama-lopchan-5504901a7/



https://github.com/kiranlamalopchan

Skills:

- Python
- Python Django
- .Net Programming
- Java
- JavaScript Framework
- Web Development (HTML, CSS, JavaScript)
- Database Management(MySQL, Postgress)

Education:

Jan 2019 – Aug 2022

Bachelor of Science: Computing

IIMS College (UCSI University) Dhobidhara, Kathmandu, Nepal

Aug 2015 - Oct 2010

Higher Secondary: Computer Science

Kathmandu Unified Secondary School – Chabahil-7, Kathmandu, Nepal

Apr 2005 – May 2015

School Leaving Certificate

Children's Liberty English Boarding School – Jorpati, Kathmandu, Nepal

Kiran Lama

SUMMARY

To seek and maintain full-time position that offers professional challenges utilizing interpersonal skills, excellent time management and problem-solving skills. Dedicated programmer known for streamlining Python development processes by exploiting open-source web frameworks. Specializes in applying Django to complex database assets with strong web presences. Comfortable taking over ongoing administration processes or designing customized administration models.

WORK HISTORY

Sep 2022 – Mar 2023

Front End Developer (Internship)

Webmalaya Tech Enterprise, Kathmandu

- Worked on design and development of modern websites using HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Improved and scaled webservices using cloud technologies
- Responsive design and UI interfaces
- Proven ability to learn quickly and adapt to new situations.
- Proved successful working within tight deadlines and a fast-paced environment.
- Managed time efficiently in order to complete all tasks within deadlines.
- Demonstrated strong organizational and time management skills while managing multiple projects.

Jan 2018 - Sep 2018

Computer Teacher

Ekata James English Academy +2, Gokarneshwor-5, Kathmandu

- Managing the computer lab and ensuring that all equipment is properly maintained and functioning.
- Evaluate student progress and provide feedback to students and parents.
- Teaching basic computer skills such as how to use a mouse and keyboard, navigate through the operating system, open and close applications.
- Developing lesson plans that incorporate the use of technology in the classroom.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Python Django Training
 - (Aug 2022) 3 Month